https://www.maverickgaming.com/privacy

Releases
Maverick Gaming Privacy PolicyJune 16th, 2020IntroductionMaverick Gaming LLC (“Maverick” or “We” or “Us”) has a strong commitment to providing excellent service to all of our customers (“Users”), including respecting their concerns about privacy. We understand that visitors to our website may have questions about whether and how this website collects and uses information and are committed to protecting your privacy. In support of this, we only use the personally identifiable information (“personal information” or “personal data”) that you provide in accordance with the terms outlined below. This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) covers any personal information we obtain when you visit us, use our services, or access the features on the websites that Maverick owns or controls (today or in the future), including https://www.maverickgaming.com/ and our mobile app (the “App”, together with the websites, collectively referred to as the “Sites”). You can access the Sites in many ways, including from a computer or mobile phone, and this Policy will apply regardless of the means of access. This Policy also governs the use of personal information we obtain from you from any third-party site or application where we post content or invite your feedback or participation (“Third Party Sites”). Maverick cannot control the privacy policies or practices of Third-Party Sites, of companies Maverick does not own or control, or of people Maverick does not employ or manage. You should always check the privacy policies of Third-Party Sites and your privacy settings.Personal Information We CollectWe collect personal information about you in different ways and from various sources.  This includes, without limitation, when you visit our websites, enroll in our loyalty program, submit a credit application, submit an employment application, check-in and stay with us, play at our casinos, attend group events or meetings, dine at our property, use the services offered at our property, complete surveys, shop at our retail stores, interact with us through our social media pages, register for Wi-Fi on our property, or contact us by email or phone (collectively, the ”Channels”).Personal Information You ProvideDepending on the Channels you use and the nature of your interactions with us, you may provide us with certain types of personal information, including:Contact information such as name, email address, postal address, fax number, and telephone number;Demographic information such as age, date of birth, education, profession, marital status, and gender;Billing and financial information such as your payment card number, expiration date, security code, delivery address, and billing address;Government-issued ID information such as your passport, driver’s license, or other government-issued ID, which you may provide, for example, at check-in or when playing at our casino;User account information such as username and password, and loyalty account number and PIN provided when you sign up for rewards program;Travel itinerary details such as arrival and departure information, flight number and details, points of origin and destination, and group information;Preference information such as food and beverage preferences, dietary information, and special requests;Content such as photos, comments, feedback, and other content you provide;Credit application information such as name and contact information, Social Security number, employment information, financial information, other lines of casino credit in your name, and other information provided in connection with your credit application if you apply for credit with us;Employment application information such as name and contact information, employment history, Social Security number, education, training and skills (including licenses and certificates), background check information, proof of eligibility to work in the United States, military service, and any other information provided in connection with an application if you apply for a job with us; andAny other personal information you provide through the Channels. Providing your personal information to us is voluntary on your part. If you choose not to provide us certain information, we may not be able to offer you certain products and services, and you may not be able to access certain features of the Channels.Personal Information Obtained from Other SourcesIn addition to the personal information you provide to us directly, we may obtain from other sources additional personal information about you, including:Friends and family-provided information such as information that your friends or family provide to us about you in connection with their reservations;Publicly available information such as name, contact information, content and online activity that we obtain from publicly available sources (such as public databases) and social media platforms you interact with; Device information such as geolocation data and other location information derived from your IP address, country, and zip code;Data collected by cookies and similar technologies such as information about your online activities, devices, browsing actions, and usage patterns across the Channels and third-party websites that we obtain through the use of cookies, web beacons, and similar technologies (see the Cookies and Similar Technologies section below);Video and Audio information such as images, video, and audio data that may be collected or processed through our security cameras, closed-circuit television, recorded phone lines, and other technologies, where permitted by law;Biometric information such as digital images; and Data from third-party sources such as personal information we obtain from our third-party service providers (including data aggregators and data cleansing companies), business partners (including travel agencies, event organizers and travel booking platforms), and marketing partners.How we use Personal InformationMaverick collects and uses Users’ personal information for the following purposes:To personalize user experience;To facilitate purchases and transactions; To facilitate reservations; To improve our Sites;To improve customer service;To share your information with third parties (see “How we share personal information” section below);To administer a content, promotion, survey or other Sites feature;To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them;To send periodic emails or mobile/SMS messages; and If a User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via our Sites or email us directly at privacy@maverickgaming.com.We may also use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Sites.If you apply for a job through our Sites, we may also use the information to:Assess qualifications and personal experience to determine if it meets specific job requirements; andHelp us inform candidates of future openings at Maverick.Cookies and Similar TechnologiesWe collect information about how you use our Sites by setting and accessing cookies on your computer. A cookie is a small piece of information sent by our Sites that is saved on your hard drive by your computer's browser. The cookie holds information our Sites may need to personalize or enhance your experience and to gather statistical data, such as which pages are visited, the Internet provider's domain name and the addresses of the sites visited immediately before coming to and immediately after leaving the Sites. The information in the cookie lets Maverick trace "clickstream" activity (i.e., the paths taken by visitors to our Sites as they move from page to page) to enable us to better serve our customers by revealing which portions of our Sites are the most popular. We may link the anonymous visitor ID from your cookie to a user ID in our database to help us analyze web traffic and statistics. From time to time, other companies may help us with data research and analysis, but they will be prohibited from using that data for any other purpose. You may disable cookies on your browser. Please review your browser's instructions for doing so. Note that certain features of the Sites may not be available if you delete or reject cookies.We may use pixel tags (also called web beacons or clear gifs) on our Sites. They can help us analyze what our customers like to do on our Sites and the effectiveness of our features and advertising. They can also help us customize your browsing experience. We may use information collected through pixel tags or tracked links in combination with your personal information. We may also combine personal information you provide to Maverick with other personal information (such as purchase history and demographic information). If we work with other companies to help us track, collect and analyze this information, they will be prohibited from using this information for any other purpose.How We Share Personal InformationWe may share your information with third parties:to help us operate our business and the Sites or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys for those limited purposes; to verify your eligibility for services;to protect payment transactions against fraud or identity theft; and to provide you with offers and marketing that may be of interest to you. How We Protect Your Personal Information We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and other data stored on our Sites. Sensitive and private data exchange between the Sites and its Users happens over a Secure Socket Layers (“SSL”) secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures.Accounts, Password and PIN SECURITYMaverick may allow Users to select a password and account designation to access his or her online player’s club account.  You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your password and account and are fully responsible for all activities that occur under your password and account.  You agree to: (i) notify Maverick immediately of any unauthorized use of your password or account or any breach of security, and (ii) ensure that you fully exit from your account at the end of each session.  By accessing a player’s club account online, you expressly agree not to use anyone else's password or PIN on the Site or provide your password or PIN to any other individual.  Maverick is not liable for any loss or damage arising from your failure to comply with this provision.  Your PIN associated with your player’s club account should only be known to you and is stored in encrypted format.  If you forget or lose access to your PIN, you will need to appear in person at the Rewards Center and request for your PIN to be reset. Retention of Your Personal InformationTo the extent permitted by applicable law, we typically retain personal information we obtain about you for as long as it is needed (1) for the purposes for which we obtained it and in accordance with the terms of this Policy, which generally means that we will keep your personal information for the duration of our relationship or as long as you are enrolled in our loyalty program; (2) to take into account applicable statute of limitation periods and comply with applicable laws; or (3) for legitimate business purposes to the extent permitted by applicable law.  As described in the “Withdrawing Consent to Use” section of this Policy, to the extent provided by the law of your jurisdiction, you may request that we delete your personal information or restrict the processing of such information by contacting us as indicated below.Children’s Personal Information & Legal Gaming AgeWe do not permit gaming at our properties or loitering in casino areas for persons under the age of 21. Maverick does not knowingly solicit or collect personal information on the Site from children under the age of 13 without prior verifiable parental consent. If Maverick learns that, despite these measures, a child under the age of 13 has submitted personally identifiable information to Maverick through the Site, it will take reasonable measures to delete such information from its records and to not use such information for any purpose (except where necessary to protect the safety of the child or others as required by law). Notice to EU ResidentsThis Policy is intended to provide adequate and consistent safeguards for the handling of personal information in accordance with Directive 95/46/EC of the European Parliament and of the Council of 24 October 1995 on the protection of individuals with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data (the “Directive”) and all the relevant transposing legislation of the Directive in the European Union/European Economic Area, the Swiss Federal Data Protection Act, as such laws may from time to time be amended and valid during the application of this Policy, the Privacy Shield, and any other privacy laws, regulations and principles concerning the collection, storage, use, transfer and other processing of personal data transferred from the European Economic Area or Switzerland to the United States including but not limited to the Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (the “General Data Protection Regulation”) as of its entry into force on 25 May 2018.California Consumer Privacy StatementIf you are a California resident, you have the right to request information from us regarding the way Maverick shares certain categories of personal information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes, in addition to the rights set forth above. Under California law, you have the right to send us a request at the designated address listed below to receive the following information:The categories of information we disclosed to third parties for their direct marketing purposes during the preceding calendar year;the names and addresses of the third parties that received the information; andif the nature of the third party's business cannot be determined from their name, examples of the products or services marketed.This information may be provided in a standardized format that is not specific to you. The designated email address for these requests is: privacy@maverickgaming.com.Withdrawing Consent to UseIf, after permitting use of your personal information, you later decide that you no longer want Maverick Gaming to include you on its mailing list or otherwise contact you or use your personal information in the manner disclosed in this Policy or at the Site, simply tell us by sending an e-mail to privacy@maverickgaming.com, or by clicking on the “Unsubscribe” button at the bottom of our email communication to you.  Additionally, you may send an email to privacy@maverickgaming.com with the phrase “Privacy Opt-out: Company Mailings” in the subject line, or write to us at the address provided below, and we will remove you from Maverick’s mailing list.Exceptions to the Privacy PolicyMaverick Gaming has three exceptions to these limits on use of personal information:(1) Maverick Gaming may monitor and, when we believe in good faith that disclosure is required, disclose information to protect the security, property, assets and/or rights of Maverick Gaming from unauthorized use, or misuse, of the Site or anything found at the Site.(2) Maverick Gaming may disclose information when we reasonably believe we are required to do so by law, or in connection with a subpoena or government request; however, only to the extent necessary and in a manner that seeks to maintain the privacy of the individual.(3) Maverick Gaming may transfer data in the event of the sale of the entire company or a majority of its assets, or in a merger or acquisition of the company. How to Contact UsFor questions or comments regarding this Policy, or to update your preferences, contact us using either of the following options:EMAIL: privacy@maverickgaming.comMail:  3300 West Desert Inn, Las Vegas Nevada 89102 Attention:  Maverick Gaming Compliance Department
Press Releases
